[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "ஆர்ப்பாட்டம்",
    "answers": ["ஆர்ப்பாட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "புல்லாங்குழல்",
    "answers": ["புல்லாங்குழல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "கேலிச்சித்திரம்",
    "answers": ["கேலிச்சித்திரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "மாரடைப்பு",
    "answers": ["மாரடைப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "நுழைவாயில்",
    "answers": ["நுழைவாயில்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "தரவரிசை",
    "answers": ["தரவரிசை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "பேராசிரியர்",
    "answers": ["பேராசிரியர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "குடியுரிமை",
    "answers": ["குடியுரிமை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "பூச்சாடி",
    "answers": ["பூச்சாடி", "பூங்கொத்து", "பூக்கள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "தொலைக்காட்சி",
    "answers": ["தொலைக்காட்சி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "விளக்கு",
    "answers": ["விளக்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "விளையாட்டுப் பொருள்",
    "answers": ["விளையாட்டுப் பொருள்", "கார் பொம்மை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "குவளை",
    "answers": ["குவளை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "முக்காலி",
    "answers": ["முக்காலி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "இருக்கை",
    "answers": ["இருக்கை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "மூக்குக் கண்ணாடி",
    "answers": ["மூக்குக் கண்ணாடி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "கால்சட்டை",
    "answers": ["கால்சட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "புத்தகம்",
    "answers": ["புத்தகம்", "புத்தகங்கள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "தொகுப்பாளர்",
    "answers": ["தொகுப்பாளர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "சொற்றொடர்",
    "answers": ["சொற்றொடர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "வண்ணக்கிளி",
    "answers": ["வண்ணக்கிளி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "தின்பண்டம்",
    "answers": ["தின்பண்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "பயணச்சீட்டு",
    "answers": ["பயணச்சீட்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "கருப்பொருள்",
    "answers": ["கருப்பொருள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "வழித்துணை",
    "answers": ["வழித்துணை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "மனநிறைவு",
    "answers": ["மனநிறைவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "கலப்படம்",
    "answers": ["கலப்படம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "பரிமாணம்",
    "answers": ["பரிமாணம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "வரவேற்பு",
    "answers": ["வரவேற்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "கொண்டைக்கடலை",
    "answers": ["கொண்டைக்கடலை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "முழக்கவரி",
    "answers": ["முழக்கவரி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "முந்திரிப்பருப்பு",
    "answers": ["முந்திரிப்பருப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "விசாரணை",
    "answers": ["விசாரணை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "நாடாளுமன்றம்",
    "answers": ["நாடாளுமன்றம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
